Contact

alisha3283@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alishasethi-02243031 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Strategy
Project Management
Continuous Process Improvement

Certifications

Certified Lean Facilitator
Lean Six Sigma Green Belt
Certification
UGC NET Qualified

Honors-Awards

Rookie of the Year ACE Award ACE Award Best QA Mentor

Alisha Sethi

CSSGB, CLF, Project Manager, Quality Leader, Process Expert, Mentor, Coach

Gurgaon

Summary

Experienced research and analytics professional with a demonstrated history of working in the financial/market services/ healthcare/pharma industry with experience in strategy formulation, analysis, and research. Mentoring and managing performance of new team members with a keen focus on quality.

Experience

S&P Global Market Intelligence 8 years 2 months

Senior Research Associate November 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months) Gurgaon, India

- -Engaged in continuous process improvement through reworking of workflows
- -Conducting regular studies for process optimization and effective engagement of all employees
- -Identifying Lean opportunities and preparing Lean charter and implementing waste reduction strategies in various workflows and tools
- -Responsible for high worth and critical client tasks.
- -Involved in implementation of automation and lean initiatives.
- -UAT testing for collection tool migration by creating and testing user stories
- -Coordinating with Scrum teams for software testing
- -Implementation of 7 qc tools and Kaizen events
- -Handling multiple guideline and more than 50 crucial datapoint related queries for all researchers
- -Involved in feedback and quality tracking of team members
- -Responsible for software testing for seamless migration between different collection tools.
- -Directly handling the performance of new team members
- -Involved in Process guideline formulation and documentation
- -Coordinating with multiple stake holders for resolving inter-team dependencies

- -Engaged in Database Monitoring, updating, researching, and quality assurance
- -Involved in collating public sector companies profiles

Research Associate 2

June 2014 - October 2017 (3 years 5 months)

Gurgaon, India

- -Carrying out External Quality Audit of the team across multiple data sets.
- -Consolidating the monthly statistics of External Quality Audit and presenting the results to senior management
- -Conducting training sessions for new joinees and shadowing them for initial months in the team

Research Associate 1

July 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 11 months)

Gurgaon, India

- Conducting Entity Validations Research and Analytics for North American, European, and Asian companies
- Conducting Business Research for a wide range of industries, including Finance, Healthcare, Information Technology, Pharmaceutical, Biotechnology, Engineering, Mining, etc.
- -Analyzing various financial market transactions in the domains of Mergers and Acquisitions and Private Equity.
- -Analyzing trade documents and annual filings.

Bharti Airtel

Marketing Intern

April 2011 - June 2011 (3 months)

Gurgaon

-Conducted usage profile analysis of telecom sector across NCR and recommended business development strategies.

Alka Chemicals and Industries Private Limited

Co-Chief Executive Officer

2007 - 2009 (2 years)

Chandigarh Area, India

- -Designed and strategized the goal of the company.
- -Developed clients
- -Expanded business in North and West India
- -Negotiated client contracts and established business divisions

Education

Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology MBA, MARKETING+ FINANCE · (2010 - 2012)

Panjab University
B.E., B.TECH, BIOTECHNOLOGY · (2006 - 2010)